export const QuestionData = [
  {
    question: "How is the learning process at Street English School?",
    answer:
      "The training process at Street English School begins with determining the level of English language proficiency and analyzing the needs of your employees. After that, we develop an individual program that takes into account the specifics of your business and training goals. Classes can be held in a convenient format for you - individually, in groups or online. Our teachers use modern methods and interactive materials to make learning effective and interesting. We measure progress regularly so you can see real results.",
  },
  {
    question: "What forms of training do you offer?",
    answer: "Individual, group, couples, speaking club, corporate training",
  },
  {
    question: "Can the training program be adapted to your business?",
    answer:
      "Of course you can, we develop a personalized training program exactly according to your request and ultimate goal",
  },
  {
    question:
      "How is the level of English proficiency of employees determined?",
    answer:
      "After the first lesson, we send a test to determine your level, also the level can be determined using our chatbot",
  },
  {
    question: "Is it possible to conduct classes online?",
    answer: "Yes, our school specializes in online learning",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the duration of the course and the number of classes?",
    answer:
      "32 lessons the duration is from 4 to 8 months approximately, it all depends on how many times a week the student practices",
  },
  {
    question: "Is it possible to change the schedule of classes if necessary?",
    answer:
      "Yes, of course we adapt to your schedule and are flexible in case of changes",
  },
  {
    question: "What materials are used during training?",
    answer: "Padlet or Kalyna additional sources if necessary",
  },
  {
    question: "How can we measure the progress of our employees?",
    answer: "I don't know the answer",
  },
  {
    question: "Do you provide certificates after completing the course?",
    answer:
      "Yes, of course, the certificate certifies that you have completed training",
  },
];
